Kann es nach dem 7. Oktober noch Frieden geben?
"Will there be peace"?
If it was up to Israel,
we had it a long time ago.
But it is not up to us.
There were a few attempts throughout history,
including right now.
Radical Islamists are not looking for peace,
period.
Always...
when people ask me "what should happen with Gaza?",
in my opinion, it shouldn't be us
or the United States that goes to help there.
It should be
moderate Muslim countries that are strong enough,
and that they are moderate enough,
to stop the horrible indoctrination
that is going on over there.
To make a big change and to bring to the people
the same prosperity that people enjoy
in more stable countries.
Countries that function, that don’t...
I must tell you this,
this example is brilliant:
Covid...
Covid happened,
right about when the Abraham Accords were taking place,
and as a gesture of goodwill,
The UAE decided they are going to donate,
I think it was 1. 5 million vaccines, to the Gaza Strip
and to the West Bank.
They said "No",
"We’re not taking it from you".
The UAE, that you can see
on their people how good rulers they are,
because you see the situation over there,
and how free the people are,
and how happy and...
They were in complete shock.
They're like "There's a pandemic on the loose",
"and we give you 1. 5 million vaccines for your people",
"and you’re not taking it because of your ego!",
they were completely shocked,
but it also
gave them a good picture of who they're dealing with.
This is a terror organization.
Wake up, it’s a terror organization,
and it’s about time that the entire world will stand up
firmly and fiercely against that horrible
terror groups that are around the world.
We should not accept terror.
I see people around the world supporting terror groups,
I'm going to..., it really...
I can’t even...
I don’t have a reply to that,
and that is amazing because you all know that
I have replies for everything.
But for that one I really can’t.
I can’t even think about what to say to these people.
"Have you all gone mad?"
Do you see the people
in Gaza what they're going through by their own regime?
Do you understand how many people in the last two years
were murdered by Hamas?
We know some of the stories.
We know people that tried to speak up,
and they were butchered and tortured,
and remains were put on the threshold of their family.
So people will see and
be afraid to do anything,
will despair. So how can you,
How on earth can anybody support that?
How on earth?
It really troubles me,
because if you look back at history,
look at World War 2 for example,
there were about half a million
British people that died,
about half a million Americans,
and about 20 million Russians,
and people from the Soviet Union.
And it took the human race decades,
decades, to realize that
Stalin was mass murdering his own people.
Decades to realize that.
Because we don’t think about it.
How did Monty Python say?
"No one expects the Spanish Inquisition"
You’re not thinking about things like that.
But, it happens.
It happens. And we have a few examples from history.
And people need to be a little bit more,
need to have a little bit more critical thinking.
A little bit more critical thinking,
when they say that I'm an occupier with
A 7 long hour drive land.
People have to have a little bit more critical thinking.
around the world.
That's it. I've got nothing more to say.